teamlab.com 2012-06-17

# Privacy - TeamLab

Since your privacy is important to us, Ascensio System SIA has created this statement in order to let you know our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Ascensio System SIA website [http://www.teamlab.com](http://www.teamlab.com/). By using our website you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

##  Information Collection 

Ascensio System SIA collects information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") in case you choose to register with TeamLab service. We require your first and last names, as well as your email address in order to authenticate users and provide access to TeamLab accounts.

If you choose not to register or provide Personal Information, you can still use our website anonymously. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration. Only the domain name from which you access the Internet, the Internet address and the date and time you access our website are logged. Ascensio System SIA uses this information to analyse trends and to measure the number of visitors of our website.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your time spent at our website, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our website users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use this information for any other purposes.

##  Use of Personal Information 

When a user submits Personal Information, it is kept on a private server not accessible from the Internet. This limits the possibility of any malicious use of your Personal Information.

Ascensio System SIA may share non-personal, summary information regarding TeamLab users with partners or other third parties. However, we will not share any individual customer information outside of the contracted partners and third parties without first receiving the individual's prior written approval. In short, Ascensio System Limited does not sell registrant information to lists. 

Ascensio System SIA may send you tips on using TeamLab, notify you of and get your feedback on upcoming releases or new services offered. The users are able to unsubscribe from the mailing list any time after receiving the first information message.

TeamLab account can be deactivated temporarily or deleted permanently at any time using the appropriate options in portal settings. 

##  Underage 

Ascensio System SIA does not intentionally collect Personal Information from persons, who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to Ascensio System SIA via the website, with the exception if such activities are allowed by applicable law of your country.

##  Intellectual Property Rights 

Ascensio System SIA does not claim any ownership of any of the content stored on your TeamLab portal, including texts, links, photos, video, or other data.

##  Public Areas 

Ascensio System SIA may create, host and provide discussion forums, newsgroups, blogs or other public environments to TeamLab users and general public. Any information disclosed in blogs or forums is considered public and each user is responsible for and should exercise caution when disclosing any Personal Information in such areas. Ascensio System SIA is not responsible for any action taken as a result of information presented or received in such areas. 

##  Links to Other Sites 

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Ascensio System SIA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit, as the Privacy Policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our privacy statement applies solely to [http://www.teamlab.com](http://www.teamlab.com/)

##  Use of "Cookies" 

During your visit to our website, so-called "cookies" are saved to your computer. These "cookies" register information about navigation of your computer on our website (loaded pages, date, time of day and length of visit etc.) which we can access during your next visit in order to adapt the website to your personal requirements and optimize loading times. We also use this information to enter your data into enquiry forms and suchlike so that you do not need to fill them in yourself again and again.

We never store passwords or similarly sensitive data in cookies. The use of cookies is common and advantageous. Cookies are used on most larger websites. By indicating how and when visitors use a website, cookies aid us in finding out which areas are popular and which areas are not. Many improvements and updates are based on information supplied by cookies. Cookies can also help us to personalize web content and meet the demands of our visitors.

Our website does not use cookies to collect Personal Information from your computer that was not initially sent as a cookie.

You have the option to control the acceptance of cookies yourself and, if you wish, to block them entirely by configuring your browser as follows: If you use the Internet Explorer to surf the net: In the "Tools" menu, click "Internet Options", select the "Privacy" tab and click "Advanced". Here, you can "Block" cookies or set up a "Prompt". The latter setting allows you to decide from occasion to occasion whether you would like to accept a cookie or not.

##  Passwords 

Your account is password-protected so that you have secure access to your TeamLab portal and Personal Information stored on your website. It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their password. The default password sent to your email address upon registration should be changed to the one known by you only at the first entry of the portal. We do not take responsibility for any undesirable information disclosure due to password insecurity. 

Ascensio System SIA has an internal security system which encrypts customer passwords to protect them from being divulged or accessed by anyone other than you. Neither Ascensio System SIA employees nor any of its contractors can access your password. We will not ask you for your password via email, phone nor using any unsolicited ways. 

##  Privacy Policy Updates 

Ascensio System SIA may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to review this privacy statement for any changes occasionally. If under any such update significant changes are made to the way in which we treat your Personal Data, we will inform you of such change via email or by posting a note on our website. 

##  Further Questions 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, feel free to email us at [ info@teamlab.com](mailto:info@teamlab.com).
